A Guide to The Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia Committee Records, 1972-1992
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia Committee Records 1972-1992
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-1/1/3.921
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1992 July 15.
Contents List
- Administrative Review 1981 Nov 20 (Box 1)
- Athletics 1969-1985 (Box 1)
- Audit Committee Correspondence 1988 Dec 29 (Box 1)
- Audit Committee Correspondence 1989-1991 (Box 1)
- Audit Committee Meeting (Volume I) 1986 Jan 30 (Box 1)
- Audit Committee Meeting (Volume II) 1986 Jan 30 (Box 1)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1986 Mar 20 (Box 1)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1986 Mar 29 (Box 1)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1986 Oct 2 (Box 1)
- Audit Committee Meeting (Volume II) 1987 Jan 29 (Box 2)
- Audit Committee Meeting (Volume I) 1987 Jan 29 (Box 2)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1987 May 28 (Box 2)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1987 Oct 1 (Box 2)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1988 Jan 21 (Box 2)
- Audit Committee Meeting (Volume II) 1988 Jan 21 (Box 2)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1988 Mar 17 (Box 2)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1988 May 26 (Box 2)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1989 Jan 26 (Box 2)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1989 Mar 30 (Box 2)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1990 Jan 24 (Box 3)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1990 May 23 (Box 3)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1989 Oct 4 (Box 3)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1991 Jan 31 (Box 3)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1991 Jan 31 (Box 3)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1990-May 1991 (Box 3)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1991-1992 (Box 3)
- Board Meetings (Executive Session) 1980-1988 (Box 3)
- Board of Visitors-General 1980-1985 (Box 3)
- Board of Visitors-Memoranda 1989 (Box 3)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence 1990 (Box 4)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1991-1992 (Box 4)
- Campaign Organizing Committee 1980-1985 (Box 4)
- Cavalier Daily Correspondence 1979-1980 (Box 4)
- College of Arts and Sciences 1971-1987 (Box 4)
- Committee on Commencement and Convocations 1986-1988 (Box 4)
- Committees 1989-1990 (Box 4)
- Correspondence to News Media R. E. Open Meetings 1979 (Box 4)
- Educational Policy Comm. Correspondence 1990 (Box 4)
- Educational Policy Comm. Correspondence 1990 (Box 5)
- Educational Policy Comm. Correspondence 1990 (Box 5)
- Educational Policy Comm. Minutes 1987-1989 (Box 5)
- Educational Policy Committee Minutes 1991-1992 (Box 5)
- Endowment Review 1988 May 10, 11 (Box 5)
- External Affairs Committee 1992 (Box 5)
- Finance Committee 1988 Dec 1 (Box 5)
- Finance Committee Correspondence 1990 (Box 5)
- Finance Committee Correspondence 1990 (Box 6)
- Finance Committee Meeting 1989 May 9 (Box 6)
- Financial Committee Minutes 1992 (Box 6)
- Freedom of Information 1973-1982 (Box 6)
- Freedom of Information 1973-1982 (Box 6)
- General Counsel 1974-1988 (Box 6)
- Health Affairs Committee Minutes 1992 (Box 6)
- Intercollegiate Athletic Programs 1989 Jun 30 (Box 7)
- Management Letter Recommendations 1986-1987 (Box 7)
- Manual Committee 1963-1966 (Box 7)
- Manual Committee Minutes 1963-1966 (Box 7)
- Memoranda to Board of Visitors 1990 (Box 7)
- Open-Meetings-General 1979 (Box 7)
- Parking 1969-1984 (Box 7)
- Regular Board Meetings 1977-1984 (Box 7)
- Report on Audit 1985-1986 (Box 7)
- Report on Audit 1986 (Box 7)
- Report on Audit 1986-1987 (Box 7)
- Report on Audit 1987 Jun 30 (Box 8)
- Report on Audit 1988-1989 (Box 8)
- Report on Audit 1989 Jun 30 (Box 8)
- Report on Audit 1990 Jun 30 (Box 8)
- Report on Audit 1990 Jun 30 (Box 8)
- Resolution, Petition and Supporting Documents of the Student Bar Association of the University of Virginia School of Law Urging Responsible Divestment of the University's Investments in South Africa 1985 Oct 11 (Box 8)
- School of Nursing 1972-1986 (Box 8)
- School of Medicine 1980-1985 (Box 8)
- Student Affairs 1980-1984 (Box 8)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Comm. Minutes 1991-1992 (Box 8)
- Student Council n.d. (Box 8)